http://www.bluegrassdavinci.com/privacy.php

Current Solar Data
CURRENT MOONphases of the moon
Privacy Policy
This is the web site of Bluegrass DaVinci Fellowship
We can be reached via .
Site Visitors
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes and records the IP address and/or hostname, browser type, operating system, screen resolution, referring page but not the email address unless provided.We collect only the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, searches conducted and/or site registrations.
The information we collect is used for internal review, used to improve the content of our Web page and used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, but never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. All orders are processed via Amazon.com, so any information you provide to Amazon.com is covered under their respective privacy policy.
Cookies and/or Web Beacons
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends and record referring sites.
Third-party cookies and/or web beacons are used to collect data in the ad serving process.
E-mail
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, or writing to us at the above address.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address, or writing to us at the above address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed or requests for information.
Ad Servers
With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of the respective ad servers.
Cookies and/or Web Beacons
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends and record referring sites.
Third-party cookies and/or web beacons are used to collect data in the ad serving process.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Security/Encryption
With respect to security: We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving financial data exchanged with our site and we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Links to Other Sites
We sometimes provide referrals to and links to other web sites from our site. Such a link should not be seen as a uniform endorsement, approval or agreement with any information or resources offered at sites you can access through our site. We are not responsible for the content or practices of third-party sites that may be linked to our sites, and no inference or assumption should be made and no representation should be inferred that we are connected with, operate or control these web sites.
Changes to Privacy Statement
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Home | Photo Albums | Links | Maywoods Dates | DaVinci Creed | Privacy Policy
Copyright © Bluegrass DaVinci Fellowship. All Rights Reserved.
